乔伊，试镜结果怎么样？ 不可思议
- Hey Joey,how'd the audition go? - Incredible!
我这回碰到导演了 你们绝对不会相信是谁的
I met the director this time and you'll never believe who it was.
谁呀？
- Who?
好，我给你们一个提示
- All right. I'll give you one hint.
华伦比提（美国最伟大的导演、剧作家和演员）
Warren Beatty.
对，只是有件事 或许会成为问题
Yeah,there's just one thing that might be kind've a problem.
我…必须要吻一个男人
See,I,uh,had to kiss this guy.
因为他可爱死了？
'Cause he was just so darn cute.
不，那是试镜的一部份 我试镜的角色是…
No,as part of the audition. See,I'm up for this part of this guy,
…男主角要亲的男人
who the main guy kisses.
你是个演员那你就放嘴去吻吧
Well,hey. You're an actor,I say you just suck it up and do it.
去做吧
Or you just do it.
我吻了，我很专业
I did do it,I'm a professional.
我第一个女友是丽萨迪芭提斯塔
My first girlfriend was Lisa DiBatista...
所以我对胡须的感觉并不陌生
so I'm no stranger to the mustache.
那有什么问题？ 我试镜完之后…
Then what's the problem?See after the scene,
…比提先生过来跟我说 “好演技，烂吻技”
Mr. Beatty comes up to me and says'good actor,bad kisser'.
你们相信吗？ 我…我吻技会烂？
Can you believe that,me not a good kisser,
那就好像…
that's like,
…好像是说特丽莎修女（有“妈妈”意思）不是个好妈妈一样
like Mother Theresa,not a good mother.
好了，谁在乎他怎么想
Well,come on,who cares what that guy thinks.
华伦比提懂什么叫做接吻？
What does Warren Beatty know about kissing Ooh.
六人行 第2季 第24集 贝瑞和明蒂的婚礼
Friends.S02E24.The.One.With.Barry.and.Mindys.Wedding
你经纪人怎么说？
Hey,what did your agent say?
接吻这回事绝对是个问题
Yep,this kiss thing is defiantly a problem,
比提先生星期一要再看一次
Mr. Beatty wants to see it again on Monday.
我得搞清楚我哪里做错了
Man,I gotta figure out what I'm doing wrong.
你们哪个女的先来吻我一下？
Oh,okay,one of you girls come over here and kiss me.
你休想 说得好
- What,forget it! - Yeah,right.
不要这样嘛，我需要帮忙啊
Come on,I need your help here.
我以前亲过他 我可以再亲一次
All right. I'll do it,I kissed him before I can do it again.
看到没？这才叫朋友
You see this,this is a friend.
开始
Uh-huh,let's go.
等等，口香糖
Oh,wait I have gum.
好，非常好，温柔而有力
Good,very good,firm but tender.
我会推荐给朋友
I'd recommend you to a friend.
那我就不知道问题出在哪里了
Then I don't know what it is. What's the problem?
乔伊，或许你是 不习惯亲男人罢了
Joey,you know,maybe your just not used to kissing men,
或许你只是神经紧绷了点
maybe you just tensed up a little,
也许你要克服这一点
maybe that's what you need to work on.
对，有道理
Yeah,that makes sense.
除非我死了
Over my dead body!
我会用他的尸体来当挡箭牌
And I'll be using his dead body as a shield.
出来吧，你听我说，你很美
Come on out,honey! I'm telling you look good!
跟她说她很美…
Tell her she looks good,tell her she looks good.
老天啊
Oh my God,
你好美喔
you look so good!
真不敢相信我得在200人面前走上红毯…
I can not believe I have to walk down the aisle in front of 200 people
…打扮得像是当你呕吐时喝的饮品
looking like something you drink when your nauseous.
那就别去啊 反正我不懂我们干嘛非去不可
So don't,I don't see why we have to go to this thing anyway,
这是你前未婚夫的婚礼
it's your ex-fiancee's wedding.
因为我答应了明蒂
Because I promised Mindy I would.
对，你也答应过贝瑞 要嫁给他的
Yeah,well you promised Barry,you'd marry him.
各位，我必须去，我是伴娘
Look you guys,I have to go,I'm the Maid-of-Honor.
我只是需要再跟这些人 共聚一堂…
And besides you know what I just need to be in a room again with these people
…而觉得不安
and feel good about myself.
有人还穿着昨天晚上的衣服耶 有人有什么艳遇吗？
Ooh-oh! Someone's wearing the same clothes they had on last night. Someone get a little action?
或许吧
- I may have.
种马（俚语）
- Woo-hoo,stuud!
她长得什么样？ 我们还没见过面呢
- What's she look like? - Well,we haven't exactly met,
只是在网上谈了一整夜而已
we just stayed up all night talking on the internet.
傻蛋
Woo-hoo,geeek!
我喜欢她，我真的很喜欢她
I like this girl,okay,I seriously like this girl,
你们也晓得 有时我会以取笑别人来保护自己
you now how sometimes I tend get a little defended and quipy...
少来了… 不会啦…
- Get out! - Nooo!
她直接批评我 她说“少来了，正经一点”
Well she totally called me on it,okay. She said,'cut it out,get real',
我照办了
and I did.
那是什么样子？
Wow! What's that like?
像这样，我
It's like this,
不开玩笑
me,no jokes.
好了，你吓死我了
All right,stop it,you're freaking me out.
是呀，我不喜欢你这样
Oh,yeah,I don't like you this way.
好吧，咱们待会儿见了
- All right,I'll see you guys later.
再见，理查 再见
- Bye,Richard.
再见，甜心，我爱你
Bye sweetie,- I love you.
我也爱你
- I love you,too.
我觉得我男朋友好棒哦
I think my boyfriend ever so dreamy,
不知道我们的婚礼 会是什么样子
I wonder what our wedding's gonna be like.
你在胡扯什么？什么婚礼？
What are you talking about? What wedding?
少来了，你们从没谈过吗？
Come on,like you never talk about that.
从来都没有
Nooo! Never!
我们只是很珍惜现在的这一刻
I mean,we're living in the moment.
就这么一次不去想 “将来会怎么样”，真是棒耶
God,it is so nice for once to not have to get all hung up on 'Where is this going?'
你怕问他吗？ 怕得不能再怕了
- Afraid to ask him? - Could not be more terrified.
我认为你应该认真考虑 结婚这件事情
Well,I think you should seriously consider the marriage thing,
再给瑞秋一次扮成泡泡糖公主的机会
give Rachel another chance to dress up like Princess Bubble Yum.
我笑的是昨晚这件搞笑的纱罗织物
I was laughing at this quip Leno made last night.
我没有笑你的裙子，我爱你
I wasn't laughing at your dress.I love you.
班尼在哪里？
Where's Benny?
他在这里？
There he is!
班尼在哪里？
Where's Benny,
他在这里
there he is.
说不定那是宝宝学说话的原因 好告诉大人们“够了”
Awww! You know that's probably why babies learn to talk,so they can tell grown ups to cut it out.
我有个问题想要问你
Hey,you know I got a question for ya.
只是件小事啦，没有压力的
Just a little thing,no pressure.
你有想到未来吗？
Did you ever,uh,like,think about the future?
当然有
Sure I do.
是吗？有想到我？
Yeah,am I in it?
亲爱的…
Honey,
…你就是我的未来
you are it.
天啊，你太走运了
Oh God,you are about to get sooo lucky.
继续说
Keep talkin'.
有时我会幻想卖掉我的诊所
Well,uh,sometimes I think about selling my practice,
我们搬到法国去
we could move to France,
做法国吐司
make French toast.
所以…
Okay,so,uh,
…我们会在法国…
we're in France,
…然后…我们会做吐司…
we're making the toast.
有没有小摇篮（与“矮脚长耳猎犬”谐音）在角落里？
Do you see a little bassinet in the corner?
猎犬吗？
Like a hound?
不是矮脚长耳猎犬
Not a basset,
是摇篮
a bassinet.
你真的需要摇篮？
You really need the bassinet?
宝宝会从狗上面掉下来呀
Well,I just think the baby would keep falling off the dog.
你没有幻想过我们有小孩吗？
Do you,uh,do you,do you not see kids in our future.
对，我爱小孩
Oh,hey,I love children,
我也有小孩
I have children.
但我不想七十岁时孩子开始上大学了咱们的生活才开始
I just don't want to be 70 when our kids go off to college,and our lives can finally start.
我现在…就要你
Look I want you,now.
太棒了
That's Great.
我们现在不需要谈这个
You know we don't need to talk about this now.
真的，我是说 这是好久好久以后的事情
Really,I mean this is,is so way,way,way,in the future,
我在说气垫船（《未来水世界》） 和猿人接管了地球以后的事情（《人猿星球》）
I'm talkin' hovercrafts and apes taking over the planet.
来嘛，钱德 我好想要这个角色哦
Come on,Chandler,I want this part soo much.
一吻就好，我不会说的
Just one kiss,I won't tell anyone.
乔伊，不就是不
Joey,no means no!
对不起，我们没看到你的羊
I'm sorry we,we don't have your sheep.
瑞秋，我觉得好可爱
Aww,Rach,I think you look cute
而你…你…
And you,uh,you,
我真想咬你一口
- you I could eat with a spoon
离我远一点，我说不了
- Get away from me I said no!
理查在楼下等
- Richard buzzed. He's waiting downstairs.
理查来了？ 我要下去跟他说再见
- Oh,Richard's here.I should run down say bye to him
再见 祝一切顺利
Bye.Good luck
跟你那个电脑妞进行如何了？
So how's your date with your cyberchick going.
那是什么？
Ooh,hey,what is all that?
网址，那是古根海姆博物馆（纽约著名美术馆）
Oh,it's a website,it's the,uh,the Guggenheim museum.
她喜欢艺术…
See,she likes art,
而我喜欢怪字…
and I like funny words.
她说“HH”是什么意思？
What does she mean by HH?
那就表示我们在“牵手”了
It means we're holding hands.
你真是太可爱了
Are you the cutest?
我想你说对了
I'm afraid I might just be.
我觉得这个很棒耶 你这么喜欢这个人…
You know,what I think is so great that you are totally into this person
…可是她可能已经九十岁了 或者是有两个头
and yet for all you know she could be like 90 years old,or have two heads,
或者可能根本是个男人
or. It could be a guy.
她不是个男的，好吗？ 我知道她不是
Okay,it's not a guy,all right,I know her.
她有可能是个大猛汉哦
It could be like a big giant guy.
老兄，我就差这么一点了 却被莫妮卡用膝盖从背后撞我
Man,I got this close to him and Monica kneed me in the back.
怎么了？
What's going on?
我们正在猜 钱德的女友是不是女的
We were just wondering if Chandler's girlfriend is a girl.
那就问她会活多久就可以了
Oh,well. Just ask her how long she's gonna live.
女人比男人长寿
Women live longer than men.
你还能再笨点吗？
How do you not fall down more?
你现在问她用什么方法避孕
Okay,ask her 'What is her current method of birth control?'
好吧
All right.
“我先生跟他的秘书有外遇”
"My husband is sleeping with his secretary."
她结婚了？
She's married!
至少我们知道她是个女的
Well at least we know she's a woman.
我真不敢相信她结婚了
I can't believe she's married.
老兄，真遗撼
Aw,man I'm sorry.
你心里一定很难受了，是吧
This must be very tough for ya,huh.
我那天读到了一篇文章说 不应该在婚礼上丢米庆祝
So,I read this article in the paper the other day that says you're not supposed to throw rice at weddings,
因为鸽子吃了会死掉
because when pigeons eat rice it kills them.
难怪寿司吧里都看不到鸽子
Oh,that's why you never see pigeons at sushi bars.
你瞧，我们很开心 是啊
- See,we're having fun. - Oh,absolutely.
你知道，我们不要去想那件事 我根本连想都不想
Yeah,you know I'm not even thinking about that thing that we're not going to be thinking about.
我也是
Neither am I.
你还好吗？
Hi,there. Are you all right?
我去上洗手间的时候，看到我结婚时，爬出去的那扇窗子
Yeah,when I was in the bathroom I saw the window that I crawled out of at my wedding,
然后我开始想我不该来的
and God,I just started thinking that I shouldn't be here,you know I shouldn't,
大家会打量我，评判我 然后就想到上一次的事
people are going to be looking at me and judging me and,and thinking about the last time.
亲爱的，你不会有事的 这是场婚礼
Sweetie,it's be gonna okay,all right. It's a wedding,
通常大家都会注意新娘子
generally people focus on the bride.
天啊，我知道你说得对
God I know,you're right.
好了，大家看着我，很好
All rightie,everybody look at me. Good.
时间到了，伴娘跟招待…
All right,its time. Bridesmaids and ushers
…排成两列，谢谢
let's see two lines,thank you.
咱们婚礼后见了
Okay,I'll see you after the thing.
祝你好运 谢谢
- Okay,good luck - Thank you
你为什么不告诉我啊？
Why the hell didn't you tell me!
对不起，我不知道应该怎么做
I'm sorry. What was I supposed to do
站起来大叫 “瑞秋，你的屁股露出来了”？
stand up and shout 'Hey,Rachel,your butt is showing!'
是的，你说总好过贝瑞的叔叔说
Yeah! Better you than Barry's uncle!
天啊，真丢脸
Oh my God this is sooo humiliating.
我想唯一比这个还要丢脸的…
I think the only thing that tops that was,was,
就是我八年级在全校面前唱《科巴卡巴纳》那次了
was when I was in the eight grade and I had to sing the Copa Cabana in front of the entire school.
我大概唱了两句就逃走了
I think I got about two lines into it before I ran and freaked out.
天啊，我悲惨的一天再现眼前
Oh my God,my entire life is flashing before my eyes.
瑞秋，听着 我记得没那么糟的
Rach,hey look,I remember that,it wasn't so bad.
罗斯，你不用说好听话给我听 你已经追到我了
Oh Ross,would you stop,you got me,I'm dating you.
温伯格先生，温伯格太太，你好
Oh hi,Mr. Wineburg,hi Mrs. Wineburg.
很高兴又看到你了，亲爱的
It's so wonderful to see you again,my dear,
老实说 我没想到会看到那么多
in fact I hardly expected to see so much.
你说你什么都没看到的 我说过很多话
You told me you didn't see anything.I tell ya a lot things!
真高兴又看到你出来走动了 亲爱的
Well it's wonderful to have you up and about,again,dear.
好好保重
Stay well.
类似刚刚那种话 我今天已经听到三次了
Okay,now that is the third time someone has said something like that to me today.
瑞秋…
Rach! Rach!
天啊，我结婚了… 我知道
- Oh my God,I'm married! - I know.
我是贝瑞亨特-法伯太太了
I'm Mrs. Dr. Barry Hunter hyphen Farber.
我好以你为傲，明蒂
Oh honey,I'm so proud of you,Min.
明蒂
Min.
瑞秋，你还在
Oh Rach,you're still here,
我们婚礼的这个时候 他们已经在收碗盘了
at our wedding,they were packing up the chopped liver about now.
是呀，我爱那个故事
Yeah,I love that story.
我有个问题要问你们
Um,I got a question for you guys.
为什么大家一直说 高兴看到我出来走动？
Why do people keep is saying that is good to see me up and about?
在你逃婚之后…
Well uh,after you ran out on your wedding,
…贝瑞的父母告诉大家说…说你疯了
Barry's parents told people that you were sort of....insane.
疯了？
Insane!
梅毒引起的
...from the syphilis.
什么？
What?!
那我该说什么？ 你不再爱我了？拜托
Yeah,what are they gonna say？You didn't love me anymore. Come on.
你的选择就只有那个和梅毒吗？
Your choices were that or syphilis?
亲爱的，至少这样会让你的屁股秀看起来很合情合理
Sweetie, at least this puts your whole tushy show into perspective.
安吉拉？我是乔伊
Angela? Joey Tribiani.
你今晚做什么？
Listen,what are ya doing tonight?
我知道你在跟他交往 我在想或许你可以带他来…
I know your seeing that guy,I was thinking maybe you could bring him.....
你还不回答她吗？ 她已经放了十次话过来了
Aren't you gonna answer her,that's like the tenth bing-bong message she sent.
她想知道怎么了
- She wants to know what's wrong?
怎么了？ 你结婚了，就是这回事！
- What's wrong? What's wrong?You're married that's what's wrong.
天啊
- Oh,my. - What?
她想要跟你见面
She wants to meet you in person.
菲比，你听我说 我也想见见她本人
Hey,look,Phoebe I wanted to meet her in person too,
但她结过婚了，她有一个丈夫
okay,but she's married,she has a husband.
如果这个丈夫不适合她呢？ 你才适合她呢？
What if the husband person is the wrong guy,and you are the right guy.
这种机会不是常有的
I mean you don't get chances like this all the time,
如果你现在不见她，八十岁时会气得踢自己的屁股…
if you don't meet her now,you're gonna be kicking yourself when your 80
…这个动作很难 而且会摔断髋骨
which is hard to do,and that's how you break a hip.
我不知道
I don't know.
听，这是一个爱着你的女人的乒乓声
Listen. Those are the bing-bongs of a woman in love with you.
好吧，我见她
Okay,I'll do it!
太棒了 穿上鞋子然后走出去见见她
Oh,yeah! Okay! Great!Go,man,go put on your shoes,and,and march out there and meet her!
老天，不，等等… 你必须先洗个热水澡因为 哟…
Oh,wait,no,no you have to take a shower,'cause,eww.
不，你已经知道你怎么回答她了，所以先回答她的问题
No,you know what you have to answer her,answer her first.
不…你…你先煮咖啡 因为太大压力了
No,no,you know what make some coffee 'cause its too much.
好了，拜托再一次嘛 我这次会丢进去的
Okay,one more,please. Come on,I'm gonna get it in this time,I will.
好吧，最后一次
Okay,last chance.
再一次，很抱歉
Again,I'm sorry.
知道吗？ 或许我不需要有孩子
You know what,maybe I don't need to have children.
或许我只是以为我需要 因为那是一种社会…
You know maybe I just think I do because that is what society,
…我是指我妈啦…
and by that I mean my mom,
…她一直让我相信我…
has always convinced me that I...
需要
I do,
我必须要有小孩，对不起 我必须要
I have to have children,I'm sorry. I just do.
请大家注意
Yo! Can I have your attention,please,
伴O要敬酒了
Best Man,making a toast here.
谢谢
Thank you.
我记得贝瑞第一次 跟瑞秋约会回来的时候
I remember when Barry got home from his first date with Rachel...
什么？你没有换乐队 却要我换演讲稿吗？
What,you hired the same band I can't use the same speech.
谢谢，非常谢谢
Thank you,thank you very much.
反正，希望你们…
Anyway,I wish you both a
…从此过着幸福快乐的日子
wonderful life together.
还有瑞秋
And Rachel...
什么？
- What.
不…我很认真的
- No,no,no now in all seriousness,
没有多少女人有这个胆子 在今天晚上回来这里
its not a lot of women would've had the guts to come back here tonight,
而且还敢露小屁股回来的 那就更少了
and even fewer,who would do it with their asses hanging out!
我想加上几句话
Uh,I like to,uh,to add something to that...
你要加什么 你要加什么 你要加什么 你要加什么…
- Why are you adding,why are you adding,why are you adding,why are you adding?
你们大半都不认识我 我是瑞秋的男朋友…
Most of you don't know me,I'm Rachel's boyfriend.
老天
Oh dear God.
…我叫罗斯
Ross,
我想说…
uh and uh,I'd just like to say
…瑞秋真的是鼓足了勇气 在今天晚上回到这里来的
that it did take a lot of courage for Rachel to come here tonight.
而且呢…
And,uh,for the record
…我想澄清瑞秋并不是 因为得了梅毒才逃婚的
she did not run out on Barry because she had syphilis.
你干什么？我这是认真的
What are you doing I'm serious.
她离开贝瑞的原因…其实很简单…她并不爱他
Uh,the reason she walked out on,on Barry is simply that she didn't love him,
所以呢，那就成就了我的美事
which incidentally worked out pretty well for me
综上所述：瑞秋 鼓足了勇气
So, to review:Rachel...took a lot of courage...
没有梅毒 并且跟我在一起
doesn't have the syphilis...and wound up with me.
干杯
Cheers!
咱们停车场见 瑞秋
- See you in the parking lot. - No,Rach!
她又再一次离开了
And once again she is out of here.
谁赌9点45分来着？
Okay who had 9:45? Um?
你知道吗，贝瑞？ 我不想走了
Ya,know what Barr,I'm not gonna leave.
我大概应该走，但是我不走
I probably should,but I'm not,
因为我答应我自己 至少要过完一次你的婚礼
see 'cause I promised myself that I would make it through at least *one* of your weddings.
我今天真正想要的只不过是…
See now,tonight,all I really wanted was
…一点优雅跟尊严来度过今晚
to make it though this evening with a little bit of grace and dignity.
我猜我们都同意 那是不可能的了
Well,I guess we can all agree that's not gonna happen.
我猜也没什么好说的了…除了…
There's nothing really left to say except....
她叫做萝拉（歌曲《科巴卡巴纳》）
"Her name was Lola.
是个歌舞女O
She was a showgirl.
头上插着…黄色羽毛，还穿着性感小洋装
With yellow feathers,feathers in her hair,and a dress cut down to there.
她…
She would..."
会热舞 会热舞，谢谢你，甜心
- Marenge,- "...marenge,thank you honey,
还会跳恰恰
and do the cha-cha.
她喜欢当明星的滋味 而东尼则是酒保
And while she like to be a star,Tony always tended bar.
在… 等等…大家一起来！
At the,wait,wait,everybody.."
好吧，我愿意
Okay,I'll do it.
你愿意什么？
You'll do what?
如果在一起必须有孩子 那就有吧
If kids is what I takes to be with you then kids it is.
天啊
Oh my God!
如果必须的话，我就再来一次
If I have to I'll,I'll do all again,
我会四点起来喂奶
I'll do the 4 o'clock feeding thing,
我会参加家长会
I'll go to the P.T.A. meetings,
当足球队的教练
I'll coach the soccer team.
真的？ 对，如果我必须的话
- Really? - Yeah,if I have to.
莫妮卡…
Monica,
…我不想失去你
I don't wanna lose you,
所以如果我必须重来一次…我还是会的
so if I have to do it all over again,then I will.
你真是我遇见过最棒的男人
You're the most wonderful man.
如果你没说那么多…"必须"的话
And if you hadn't of said 'if I have to' like seventeen times,
…那么我会说 “好吧，咱们生吧”
then I'd be saying 'okay,let's do it.'
但是你不会
But you're not.
天啊 真不敢相信我就要这么说了
Oh my God,I can't believe what I'm getting ready to say.
我想要一个孩子
I wanna have a baby,
但我不想跟一个 并不是真的想孩子的人一起生
but I don't wanna have one with someone who doesn't really wanna have one.
天啊
God.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道
I know you do.
我也是
Me too.
现在呢？
So what now?
现在我们就只有…
I guess we just
…一直跳下去
keep dancing.
她在哪里？…
Where is she,Where is she?
我有个问题，她在哪里？
Oh,hey,I have a question,where is she?
钱德，你放心吧 她会来的
Chandler,relax,Chandler,she'll be here.
她来了
Ooh,oh,oh,that's her.
对，因为生活就是那样美好
Yeah,'cause life's just that kind.
钱德，你得停止盯着门看，那就像你盯着水壶一样
Chandler,you gotta stop staring at the door. It's like a watched pot,
如果你一直盯着看的话 那扇门是永远不会沸腾的
you know if you keep looking at it then the door is to,never gonna boil.
我认为你必须试着不去…
I think what you have to do is try not to...
老天啊
Oh my God!
我的…
OH
…老…
My
…天啊
God
我的…
OH
…老…
My
…天啊
God
好吧
All right
我一直觉得好内疚，因为我想做个好朋友
I've been feeling incredibly guilty about this,because I wanna be a good friend,
该死，我是个好朋友 所以，闭嘴并且闭上眼睛
and dammit I am a good friend. So just,just shut up and close your eyes.
你真是好朋友
Wow,you are a good friend,
对了，试镜是今天早上 而我失败了
'course the audition was this morning,and I didn't get it.
但是你吻功真不错
But that was a hell of a kiss.
瑞秋是个很幸运的女孩
Rachel is a very lucky girl.